Guide to the George Mason University Office of the President records, 1949-2004
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 6: George W. Johnson, 1957-2004, (78 boxes)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Fairfax County Chair in local government, April 28, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 53)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Commonwealth of Virginia, State Corporation Commission, application of Virginia power, May 13, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 54)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Commencement, May 21, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 55)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Commencement speech, Paul VI High School, June 6, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 56)
  - George W. Johnson speech: AASCU (American Association of State Colleges and Universities) presentation, June 8, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 57)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Vision statement, June 22, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 58)
  - George W. Johnson speech: The twilight of hierarchy by Harlan Cleveland, circa 1988 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Kyungpook National University, Korea, July 1988 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Crystal City rotary, July 13, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Sub task force, August 15, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Optimists, September 1, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV) retreat, September 10, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV), September 14, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Alumni, September 15, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Statement for American Association of State Colleges and Universities (AASCU) program, September 27, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State of the University, September 29, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Mason scholars, October 3, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Driving toward greatness, October 11, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV) Commission University of 21st Century, December 5, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Northern Virginia Sun, December 7, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Untitled report, December 21, 1988 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Revenue bonds, January 1989 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Handley scholars, Winchester, VA, January 11, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - George W. Johnson speech, January 12, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Report to Board of Visitors (BOV), January 17, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Union Day, April 7, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - George W. Johnson speech: General faculty meeting, April 12, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - George W. Johnson speech: AIR speech, Baltimore, May 1, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Foundation meeting, May 8, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Fairfax County Planning committee public hearing, May 9, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Meeting, May 15, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 25)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV), May 16, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 26)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Commencement opening, May 16, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 27)
  - George W. Johnson speech: European Community Studies Association's inaugural conference banquet, May 24, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 28)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Hazel and Schar lunch, May 26, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 29)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Prince William economic tour, June 7, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 30)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Steering committee, June 14, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 31)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Al Smith, June 24, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 32)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State of the University, September 13, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 33)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Admissions recruitment video taping, September 21, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 34)
  - George W. Johnson speech: COP Richmond, September 25, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 35)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Shaping the future of higher education, November 20, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 36)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Dinner, November 30, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 37)
  - George W. Johnson speech: School of Business administration, December 5, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 38)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of trade news, outlook '89, December 6, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 39)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Arlington committee or 100, December 13, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 40)
  - George W. Johnson speech: No title, January 18, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 41)
  - George W. Johnson speech: General assembly, January 23, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 42)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Fairfax committee of 100, January 24, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 43)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Steering committee, February 9, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 44)
  - George W. Johnson speech: (Democratic?) women, March 19, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 45)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Spring general faculty meeting, April 4, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 46)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Metropolitan University conference, April 22-24, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 47)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Tour visit, May 9, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 48)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Commencement, May 19, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 49)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Public hearing on the Washington bypass, June 14, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 50)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Speech to Mason Society, June 15, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 51)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Mission statement at Board of Visitors retreat, July 28, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 52)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Freshman convocation, August 24, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 53)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State of the University, September 12, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 54)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors report, September 19, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 55)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Convocation, September 27, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 56)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Civil War reception, October 1990 (Box 92, Folder 57)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Washington Hall of Fame, October 23, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 58)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Fairfax Chamber of Commerce, November 1990 (Box 92, Folder 59)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Testimony before senate finance subcommittee on higher education, November 19, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 60)
  - George W. Johnson speech: General faculty meeting, December 3, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 61)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Southeastern Association of Colleges and Schools (SACS), December 10, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 62)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Dean's meeting, December 20, 1990 (Box 92, Folder 63)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Appropriations committee testimony, January 3, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 64)
  - George W. Johnson speech, January 21, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 65)
  - George W. Johnson speech: General Faculty meeting, March 6, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 66)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Alexandria Rotary, March 12, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 67)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Northern Virginia Institute, April 19, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 68)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Fairfax Rotary, April 30, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 69)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Montreal speech, July 17, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 70)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Senate finance, July 19, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 71)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Hunton and Williams, July 24, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 72)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Northern Virginia Institute planning meeting, August 2, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 73)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Freshman convocation, August 28, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Robinson retreat, August 29, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State of the University, September 11, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Speech for Omaha, September 13, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - George W. Johnson speech: President's remarks to Board of Visitors (BOV), September 24, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV) annual meeting, September 25, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - George W. Johnson speech: international education, Charlottsville, October 3, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Budget, October 16, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Legislative delegation, December 3, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State of the University, December 9, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Rotary, circa 1992 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Fairfax Oaks Rotary, January 6, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Rotary, January 7, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - George W. Johnson speech: No title, January 8, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Memorial service Unitarian church Arlington, February 29, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Memorial service for Joe Fisher, March 3, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - George W. Johnson speech: General faculty meeting, March 16, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - George W. Johnson speech: The economy of the 21st Century, March 19, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - George W. Johnson speech: University of Texas, Dallas, March 21, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Shenandoah University convocation, April 1, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - George W. Johnson speech: University of Nebraska, April 3, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 21)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Herndon Rotary, April 8, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 22)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Woodbridge Rotary, April 30, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 23)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Regional leadership retreat, May 1, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Arlington Historical Society, May 1, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 25)
  - George W. Johnson speech: General faculty meeting, May 6, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 26)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Arlington Rotary, May 7, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 27)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Fauquier Rotary, May 28, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 28)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Virginia University needs, June 1, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 29)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Alumni, July 8, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 30)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Freshman convocation, August 27, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 31)
  - George W. Johnson speech: General obligation bond presentation, September 9, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 32)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV) retreat, September 11, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 33)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State of the University address, September 16, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 34)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Arlington kickoff speech, October 5, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Falls Church Chamber of Commerce, October 20, 1992 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - George W. Johnson speech: VCC system annual meeting, November 19, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 36)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State of the Universe, November 30, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 37)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Legislative roundtable, December 2, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 38)
  - George W. Johnson speech: First session of executive roundtable, December 8, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 39)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Higher education decline, January 1993 (Box 93, Folder 40)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Appropriations committee, January 19, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 41)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Association of Virginia colleges annual meeting (cancelled), January 19, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 42)
  - George W. Johnson speech: General faculty meeting, February 18, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 43)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Fairfax Rotary, February 22, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 44)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State Council for Higher Education (SCHEV), March 8, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 45)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Meeting with Chinese delegation, March 30, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 46)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Vienna Chamber of Commerce, April 8, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 47)
  - George W. Johnson speech: General faculty meeting, April 19, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 48)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Venture America, April 20, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 49)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Talk to students, April 21, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 50)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Speech to staff, May 10, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 51)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Governor's symposium, June 14, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 52)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Voices of America for Higher Education, June 15, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 53)
  - George W. Johnson speech: House appropriations, July 18, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 54)
  - George W. Johnson speech: FROSH, August 26, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 55)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State of the Union address, town meeting, September 15, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 56)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Greater Washington Board of Trade, September 20, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 57)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Abingdon speech, September 23, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 58)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Jim Laue memorial, October 2, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 59)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Alumni, November 18, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 60)
  - George W. Johnson speech: General faculty meeting, December 8, 1993 (Box 93, Folder 61)
  - George W. Johnson speech: House Appropriations committee, January 12, 1994 (Box 93, Folder 62)
  - George W. Johnson speech: House Appropriations committee, January 13, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Springfield Rotary, February 22, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - George W. Johnson speech: PWI event with Rector Joe Heastie, March 23, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - George W. Johnson speech: General faculty meeting, March 30, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Quality, equity, cost, April 4, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Slide show at Century Club, April 8, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Slide show, April 8, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Learning in retirement, April 15, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Rotary speech, April 18, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Dean's and Director's meeting, May 11, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Slide show (What happened to public funding of higher education), May 17, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Northern Virginia roundtable, June 7, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - George W. Johnson speech: House appropriations committee, August 22, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Staff retreat agenda, August 24, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - George W. Johnson speech: President's Council, August 25, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Freshman convocation, August 25, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV) retreat, September 9, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Testimony before money committee, September 28, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - George W. Johnson speech: State of the University, September 28, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Time to reinvent teaching, September 28, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Brown bag seminar, October 4, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Foundation Board, October 11, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Fairfax Rotary, October 24, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Annandale Rotary, November 9, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - George W. Johnson speech: ATCC presentation, November 10, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Reorganizing meeting, November 17, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - George W. Johnson speech: GMU in 2000, December 1, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 28)
  - George W. Johnson speech: GMU Foundation cultivation, December 1, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 29)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Northern Virginia (NoVA) delegation meeting, December 5, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 30)
  - George W. Johnson speech: House appropriations committee, January 23, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 31)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Roundtable, January 26, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 32)
  - George W. Johnson speech: LRI, February 1, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 33)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Town meeting, March 7, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 34)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Meeting with MAIT students, March 20, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 35)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV) meeting, March 22, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 36)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Executive council retreat, April 19, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 37)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Town meeting, April 20, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 38)
  - George W. Johnson speech: GMU Foundation board, May 9, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 39)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Chichester meeting, May 10, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 40)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Virginia business, Higher education council, May 16, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 41)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Executive council, June 1, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 42)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Staff retreat, June 14, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 43)
  - George W. Johnson speech: President's council, July 28, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 44)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Executive council retreat, August 1995 (Box 94, Folder 45)
  - George W. Johnson speech: President's council, August 30, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 46)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV) retreat, Fall 1995 (Box 94, Folder 47)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Board of Visitors (BOV) meeting reports, September 1995 (Box 94, Folder 48)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Prince William Institute ground breaking, September 14, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 49)
  - George W. Johnson speech: General faculty meeting, September 21, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 50)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Back to school night, October 19, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 51)
  - George W. Johnson speech: House appreciations subcommittee on Higher Education, October 20, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 52)
  - George W. Johnson speech: PMW economic development, November 17, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 53)
  - George W. Johnson speech: PWM, November 20, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 54)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Century Club, November 21, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 55)
  - George W. Johnson speech: Legislative seminar, December 1995 (Box 94, Folder 56)
  - Staff meeting minutes, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 57)
  - Staff meeting minutes, 1978 (Box 94, Folder 58)
  - State Agency auxiliary, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 59)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV), 1985-1991 (Box 94, Folder 60)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Benchmark salary, proposal to restructure, 1980-1987 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Capital outlay and budget, 1990-1991 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Commission on the University of the 21st Century, 1989-1991 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Commission on the University of the 21st Century, 1990 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): UVA and VT response to the Commission on the University of the 21st Century, August 21, 1989 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Correspondence Community College project, 1987 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Correspondence, 1987 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Correspondence, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Correspondence, 1989 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Correspondence, 1990 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Council of Presidents [1 of 2], 1990-1991 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Council of Presidents [2 of 2], 1983 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Council notes, 1988-1989 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Council notes and research notes, 1988-1991 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Eminent scholars [1 of 2], 1988-1991 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Eminent scholars [2 of 2], 1984-1991 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): HJR z59 study plan outline, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Response to HJR 77, 1984 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): In-state tuition, 1983-1991 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Meeting, July 5, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Meeting, January 3, 1990 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Meeting, May 15, 1991 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Patent policy, July 30, 1987 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Proposal, education for economic security art title II, 1988 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Proposal for organizational change, June 28, 1988 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Report of the University task force, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Report on the budgeting for out of state students (draft), September 26, 1988 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Report on increases in non-educational and general fees (draft), November 23, 1988 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Reused program approval process, May 8, 1987 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Sexual assault survey, 1991 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Storage, 1980-1989 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Study group on library materials pricing policies, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Telecommunications task force, 1985-1986 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): "Three key degrees" correspondence [1 of 2], 1987-1991 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): "Three key degrees" correspondence [2 of 2], circa 1980 (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Virginia cooperative graduate engineering program, July 31, 1989 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Virginia's public schools, progress and a new agenda, 1989 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - State Water Control Board, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Steno notebook, 1985 (Box 133)
  - Steno notebook: Ann Wingblade, February 27, 1984-August 28, 1984 (Box 133)
  - Steno notebook: Ann Wingblade, August 28, 1984-February 1985 (Box 133)
  - Steno notebook: Ann Wingblade, February 1985-July 8, 1985 (Box 133)
  - Steno notebook: Ann Wingblade, November 15, 1985-May 9, 1986 (Box 133)
  - Steno notebook: Ann Wingblade, October 28, 1986-March 3, 1987 (Box 133)
  - Steno notebook: Ann Wingblade, January 4, 1987-May 18, 1988 (Box 133)
  - Steno notebook: Ann Wingblade, July 10, 1987-January 4, 1988 (Box 133)
  - Steno notebook: Ann Wingblade, May 19, 1988-November 7, 1988 (Box 133)
  - Steno notebook: Board of Visitors, April 1, 1987-April 27, 1988 (Box 133)
  - Student: Athlete exit interviews report, 1995 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Student and parent concerns, 1995 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Student and parent concerns, 1995 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Student and parent concerns, 1995 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Student and parent concerns, 1995 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Student and parent concerns, 1995 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Student concerns: Academics, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Student concerns: Academics, 1993 (Box 98, Folder 11)